Ernest F. Gray Papers 1931-2001, n.d.
Thomas Balch Library
Thomas Balch Library
Ernest F. Gray Papers, 1931-2001, n.d.
Thomas Balch Library
SC 0120
Less than 0.33 cubic feet.
The collection consists of materials collected by Ernest F. Gray including an issue of his high school newspaper, Round Hill Hi-Lights, his high school yearbook, Reveries, a program for the Leesburg Lions Club's 1960 Variety Show, an undated letter from Lizzie Swart to "a friend," and various materials from funerals including programs, prayer cards, and related correspondence.
Handley Regional Library, Winchester, VA.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection open for research.
Acquisition Information
Handley Regional Library, Winchester, VA.
Alternative Form Available
None
Accruals
2015.0180
Historical Information
Ernst Fenton Gray, also known by the nickname "Teedles," was born 12 December 1921. He attended Round Hill School, graduating in 1940. He died 8 December 2004 and is buried in Hillsboro Cemetery.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of materials collected by Ernest F. Gray including an issue of his high school newspaper, Round Hill Hi-Lights, his high school yearbook, Reveries, a program for the Leesburg Lions Club's 1960 Variety Show, an undated letter from Lizzie Swart to "a friend," and various materials from funerals including programs, prayer cards, and related correspondence.
Arrangement
Folder: Item
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Bibliography
Ancestry.com. U.S., Find A Grave Index, 1600s-Current [database on-line]. Provo, UT, USA: Ancestry.com Operations, Inc., 2012. (accessed 5/19/2016)
Ernest F. Gray Collection (SC 0120), Thomas Balch Library, Leesburg, VA
Other Finding Aid
None
Technical Requirements
None
Related Material
None
Contents List
    - Round Hill Hi-Lights, 1939 (see OM 30)
    - Reveries, Edited by the Seniors of Round Hill School, 1940
    - Access Copy of Reveries, 1940
    - Leesburg Lions Club Variety Show Program, 1960
    - Funeral Programs and Related Documents, 1980-2001, n.d.
    - Letter from Lizzie Swart, n.d.
    - Round Hill Hi-Lights, 1939